HENDRY PRASETYO

088809773289 | hendryprasetyo13@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/hendrypras | hendryprasetyo.github.io |

Bekasi, Indonesia

A bachelor degree of Computer and Network Engineering. Has great interest in work in the field of Web Development. Experienced as a Front-End and Back-End Developer working with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, and Node.js. Currently taking part in the Full-Stack Web Developer bootcamp program to deepen skills in Web Developer. A detail-oriented individual who desires a full-time opportunity in Full-Stack Web Development.

Work Experiences

Freelance Aug, 2023

Front-End Developer

- Developing websites that comply with the accessibility standards, policies and procedures
- Developing and managed web accessibility testing plans and processes, including setting up and configuring tools
- Developing the websites using React.js, Typescript, Tailwind CSS, Framer Motion

Project Experiences

Ecommerce Web - Self Project

Apr, 2023 - Present

Full-Stack Developer

- Complete features for buyers and sellers with payment gateway
- Involved in technology and design selection, bug fixing on functionality, performance, and design issues with CSS, React.js and Redux
- Developed backend logs in Node.js for restAPI and MongoDB Database

NEWS Web - Self Project

Jun, 2023 - Jul, 2023

Full-Stack Developer

- Website maintenance feature by admin
- Involved in technology and design selection, bug fixing on functionality, performance, and design issues with React is and CSS
- Developed backend logs in Node.js for restAPI and MYSQL Database

Portfolio Web - Self Project Jan, 2023

Front-End Developer

- Develop static website designs that are modern and interactive
- Involved in technology and design selection, bug fixing on functionality, performance, and design issues with React.js and CSS

Education Level

Medan, Indonesia

SMK NEGERI 3 Kota Bekasi - Bekasi, Indonesia

Jun, 2020 - Mei, 2023

Computer and Network Engineering, 81.30/100

Relevant Course Works: Database, Web Development, System, HTML, Networking

Courses, Training and Certifications

Harisenin.com - Jakarta, Indonesia

Sep, 2020 - Jan, 2024

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

- Final Project: Designing and Developing a Hotel Website and Booking Application within Three Months
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js and Node.js

Vocational School Graduate Academy - Junior Web Developer, Ministry of Communication and Informatics

Junior Web Developer (Top Performer)

Jun, 2020 - Jul, 2023

- Final Project: Designed and developed a website for a news company, Dynamic News Website, within one month
- Relevant Course works: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, React.js, Express.js and Node.js
- Certificate: Ministry of Communication and Information of the Republic of Indonesia

Skills and Other Experience

Hard skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Node.js, React.js, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind CSS, Git/Github, HTTP, MYSQL, MongoDB, Web Storage

Soft skills: Problem Solving, Quick Learning, Growth Mindset, Project Management, Time Management, Orientation to Detail, Analytical Thinking and Teamwork

Languages: English (begineer), Indonesia (Native)